good morning guys
welcome back to our channel
today we are gonna discuss on the same
topic that was in our last four videos
that we were discussing about the top
five companies
insurance companies available in united
states of america so we are adding a
special request that is prudential
insurance potential financial
specifically
and let me tell you a
company secret here
it is the most popular website most
popular insurance company of the united
states
the due to this popularity
it is the most
expensive you can say or the most
beneficial insurance company is
available
but as per our ranking in the top 16
best overall life insurance companies of
2021 prudentials ties for the 15th place
with mutual of omaha with a score of 3.6
it is narrowly outscored by rivals like
alasta
and john hancock
and protective lives which earns overall
score between 3.7 and 3.8
so let's discuss about the credentials
financials
the prudential is not just providing the
insurance police insurance but also it
is providing the investments and retire
plans as well so let's get straight up
to the plans
here are their plans get the personal
guidance and support you deserve you can
see all the plans now
how's the financial wellness how
financial education ongoing
financial tools and moreover
and also you can do one more thing if
you are individual that's fine otherwise
you can change your
personality here you are an advertiser
employer institution
or even a family whatever you are for
example let's go to the institution
so if you are an institute and you want
to secure your institute if you are a
school or any public property and you
want to secure it
so you can go with the credentials
they will charge you more but they can
provide you more facilities that you can
ever imagine
and also if you are the employer of the
prudential then you will get the hell
more benefits than the other companies
and for the becoming the employer of the
companies as from those
other insurance companies you can see
the carriers tab here as well
as in the cine that we discussed in our
third video if you haven't watched it go
to our channel you may watch it there
and hope you will find it beneficial for
you
senate the difference from the sanet was
it was protecting the planets as well it
was clearing it and here in prudential
it is providing you
retirement plans your investment plans
if you are earning good you can invest
somewhere else
and you can make some extra money
by the end of your services
here are the carriers of it
it might take a few minutes as the
websites are usually busy due to the
covet
people are usually searching for the
jobs so here we are on the carrier
websites there are multiple job
categories available
you can see if you are
actuarial corporate functional
data science finance and account invest
investment management whatever the
skills you got you can be a part of this
company
you can see their early talent your
application as well and also you can
modify the language
as per your country
your mother language
just to make yourself easy
you can distinguish by the states by the
location you can search by the keywords
for the more clarification and you can
find your best map job in your area
let's get back to our website
here we can see that
let's get back to the main page
here we are
our first website our first insurance
company
was providing some insurance regarding
the kobe 19 vaccine as well
but as as far as i cannot see it here
let's see if we can find it
the website is pretty cool
you can search
the investment